{
    "Chapter1" : {
        "topic"          : "Chapter 1 : EXPERIMENTAL CHEMISTRY ",
        "multiple_choice" : [
            {
                "question" : "who is beautiful",
                "choice" : [" cat " , "red", "dfe ", "dfd"],
                "answer" : 3
            },
            {
                "question" : "who is ugly",
                "choice" : [" this is a " , "this is b", "this is c ", "d"],
                "answer" : 1
            }
        ],

        "fill_in_the_blank" :[
            {
                "question" : " bla bla ?",
                "answer"   : ["hello","HELLO"]
            },
            {
                "question" : " bla bla ?",
                "answer"   : ["hello","HELLO"]
            }
        ],

        "true_false" :[
            {
                "question"  : "is this true or false",
                "answer"    : true
            }
        ]
        
    },

    "Chapter2" : {
        "topic"          : "Chapter 2 : ATOMIC STRUCTURE AND STOICHIOMETRY",
        "multiple_choice" : [
            {
                "question" : "who is beautiful",
                "choice" : [" this is a " , "this is b", "this is c ", "d"],
                "answer" : 3
            },
            {
                "question" : "who is ugly",
                "choice" : [" this is a " , "this is b", "this is c ", "d"],
                "answer" : 1
            }
        ],

        "fillintheblank" :[
            {
                "question" : " bla bla ?",
                "answer"   : ["hello","HELLO"]
            },
            {
                "question" : " bla bla ?",
                "answer"   : ["hello","HELLO"]
            }
        ],

        "true_false" :[
            {
                "question"  : "is this true or false",
                "answer"    : true
            }
        ]
        
    }
}